<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mars on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</title>
    <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/mars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mars on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 08:37:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/mars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Earth life originated?</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/where_earth_life_originated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2020 08:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/where_earth_life_originated/</guid>
      <description>Where Earth life originated? First of all happy new year and wish all have a good year ahead.
It was during my holiday that I started to think where possibly Earth life originated. Was it there since the beginning of time? Or aliens introduced it? Or a meteorite hit the Earth at some point and brought some microbes survived all the way?
For that, I did some search on the net, as usual, and found an interesting article from Space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phobos and Deimos, Mars moons</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/mars_moons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/mars_moons/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Recently, I have stumbled upon an article about Mars moons. To be honest, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know that Mars has any moons at all until I read the article. Anyhow, after reading the article, I decided to write a short blog post to introduce Mars moons for those, like me, who don&amp;rsquo;t know about them.
Mars moons Mars has two moons named Phobos and Deimos. Phobos is the bigger one and Deimos is the smaller.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More possibilities of life on Mars, Oxygen discovery</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/oxygen_on_mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/oxygen_on_mars/</guid>
      <description>More possibilities of life on Mars, Oxygen discovery I read a great news today. Mars Curiosity has found Oxygen on Mars. This means higher chances of microorganism life on Mars. As we already knew Methane exists on Mars that raises during summer for unknown reasons. And now Oxygen discovery hypothetically speaking means the existence of some sort of life. Or the ability to supporting life on Mars. I am very excited about it and can&amp;rsquo;t wait for more detailed findings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gorgeous Mars Curiosity pictures</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/gorgeous_mars_curiosity_pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/gorgeous_mars_curiosity_pictures/</guid>
      <description>Gorgeous Mars Curiosity pictures Well I am little bit late this time but anyhow it is an interesting news. On November first, Sol 2573, Curiosity rover has reached to a bleak mountain in mid of a crater. And from there it has sent some amazing pictures. The objective of going through this path is to understand how and when water was flowing on Mars.
Enjoy this gorgeous picture,
  Sol 2573 Mars Curiosity Rover credit: NASA/JPL-Caltech</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Possibilities of life out of the Earth</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_out_of_earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_out_of_earth/</guid>
      <description>Possibilities of life out of the Earth So NASA has confirmed hundreds of exoplanets, source. And seems more yet to come. But these planets are not so close to us. The closest ones are 50 light-years away. And available data about them are rather limited given the far distance.
This could be very disappointing. Even with the fast speed of technology advancement.
But wait, there are more viable options.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>