<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Extraterrestrial life on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</title>
    <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/extraterrestrial-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Extraterrestrial life on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:37:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/extraterrestrial-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Potential planets supporting life in solar system</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/potential_planets_supporting_life_in_solar_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/potential_planets_supporting_life_in_solar_system/</guid>
      <description>Potential planets supporting life in the solar system After a very long time, finally, I stopped procrastinating and start to write about astronomy again.
In this blog post, I go through the planets that potentially support life in our solar system. I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because scientists found new stuff recently and so many new news floating around.
Mars We are familiar with Mars, especially after successful Curiosity Rover landing. And it is getting more and more attractive as scientists make discoveries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A word on extraterrestrial life</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/a_word_on_extraterrestrial_life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 08:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/a_word_on_extraterrestrial_life/</guid>
      <description>A word on extraterrestrial life I was reading an article by Space.com titled
 Discovering Extraterrestrial Life Would Be Slow and Uncertain
 Meghan Bartels  Space.com    That made me think for a second about extraterrestrial life which could be interesting to share.
For a second, imagine that tomorrow scientists discovered a sort of life exists out of the earth. No need to be too odd like weird formed alien, just a microorganism life, very simple.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>