<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</title>
    <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Evidence of vapor water on Europa</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/vapor_water_europa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/vapor_water_europa/</guid>
      <description>Evidence of vapor water on Europa This is the second good news from our solar system this week. Two days ago, Titan, and today Europa, the Jupiter moon. As mentioned before scientists speculate the existence of a liquid ocean underneath the Europa icy surface. And today, source, they have announced that they found evidence of vapor water.
What does it mean to us? It means more possibilities of supporting life on Europa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Possibilities of life in the solar system, Saturn&#39;s moon Titan</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_on_titan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_on_titan/</guid>
      <description>Possibilities of life in the solar system, Saturn&amp;rsquo;s moon Titan Well, I have some exciting news about the possibilities of life in the solar system. But this time is not Mars or Europa, it&amp;rsquo;s about Titan, a Saturn&amp;rsquo;s moon. According to Reuters, data from NASA’s Cassini spacecraft reveals the existence of carbon in Titan. This speculates scientists about the possibilities of life under the icy ocean in Titan. My analysis, if the liquid water runs under the Titan icy ocean, the chance of microbiological life is higher than Mars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More possibilities of life on Mars, Oxygen discovery</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/oxygen_on_mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/oxygen_on_mars/</guid>
      <description>More possibilities of life on Mars, Oxygen discovery I read a great news today. Mars Curiosity has found Oxygen on Mars. This means higher chances of microorganism life on Mars. As we already knew Methane exists on Mars that raises during summer for unknown reasons. And now Oxygen discovery hypothetically speaking means the existence of some sort of life. Or the ability to supporting life on Mars. I am very excited about it and can&amp;rsquo;t wait for more detailed findings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gorgeous Mars Curiosity pictures</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/gorgeous_mars_curiosity_pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/gorgeous_mars_curiosity_pictures/</guid>
      <description>Gorgeous Mars Curiosity pictures Well I am little bit late this time but anyhow it is an interesting news. On November first, Sol 2573, Curiosity rover has reached to a bleak mountain in mid of a crater. And from there it has sent some amazing pictures. The objective of going through this path is to understand how and when water was flowing on Mars.
Enjoy this gorgeous picture,
  Sol 2573 Mars Curiosity Rover credit: NASA/JPL-Caltech</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Possibilities of life out of the Earth</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_out_of_earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_out_of_earth/</guid>
      <description>Possibilities of life out of the Earth So NASA has confirmed hundreds of exoplanets, source. And seems more yet to come. But these planets are not so close to us. The closest ones are 50 light-years away. And available data about them are rather limited given the far distance.
This could be very disappointing. Even with the fast speed of technology advancement.
But wait, there are more viable options.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A word on extraterrestrial life</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/a_word_on_extraterrestrial_life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 08:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/a_word_on_extraterrestrial_life/</guid>
      <description>A word on extraterrestrial life I was reading an article by Space.com titled
 Discovering Extraterrestrial Life Would Be Slow and Uncertain
 Meghan Bartels  Space.com    That made me think for a second about extraterrestrial life which could be interesting to share.
For a second, imagine that tomorrow scientists discovered a sort of life exists out of the earth. No need to be too odd like weird formed alien, just a microorganism life, very simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astronomy books</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/astronomy_books/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/astronomy_books/</guid>
      <description>Some astronomy books I have been following astronomy news for quite sometimes but never read a single book about it. All my knoweldge comes from news and Wikipedia. Two days ago I saw Space.com tweeted a list of Astronomy and Sci-Fi books of 2019 which I believe worth sharing,
Best Space Books and Sci-Fi for 2019 https://t.co/U4Nf3UGiZR pic.twitter.com/O4FVuIFryy
&amp;mdash; SPACE.com (@SPACEdotcom) October 30, 2019 
Actual link, here. As a starter I&amp;rsquo;m gonna do some research and pick up one for my next reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Voyagers computers are running since 1977</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/how_voyager_computers_working/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 08:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/how_voyager_computers_working/</guid>
      <description>How Voyagers computers are running since 1977 I have always been passionate about Voyager 1, 2 missions. One thing that I have never paid attention to how their computers are working and still sending data to Earth for over 40 years ago. That means Voyager computers have the highest uptime of all the time, over 15K days.
So to learn more about the Voyager computers, I did a quick search on the internet and came across this awesome video explaining how Voyager computers are designed by Aaron Cummings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>