<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Europa on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</title>
    <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/europa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Europa on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:37:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/europa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Potential planets supporting life in solar system</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/potential_planets_supporting_life_in_solar_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/potential_planets_supporting_life_in_solar_system/</guid>
      <description>Potential planets supporting life in the solar system After a very long time, finally, I stopped procrastinating and start to write about astronomy again.
In this blog post, I go through the planets that potentially support life in our solar system. I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because scientists found new stuff recently and so many new news floating around.
Mars We are familiar with Mars, especially after successful Curiosity Rover landing. And it is getting more and more attractive as scientists make discoveries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evidence of vapor water on Europa</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/vapor_water_europa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/vapor_water_europa/</guid>
      <description>Evidence of vapor water on Europa This is the second good news from our solar system this week. Two days ago, Titan, and today Europa, the Jupiter moon. As mentioned before scientists speculate the existence of a liquid ocean underneath the Europa icy surface. And today, source, they have announced that they found evidence of vapor water.
What does it mean to us? It means more possibilities of supporting life on Europa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Possibilities of life out of the Earth</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_out_of_earth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_out_of_earth/</guid>
      <description>Possibilities of life out of the Earth So NASA has confirmed hundreds of exoplanets, source. And seems more yet to come. But these planets are not so close to us. The closest ones are 50 light-years away. And available data about them are rather limited given the far distance.
This could be very disappointing. Even with the fast speed of technology advancement.
But wait, there are more viable options.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>