<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Titan on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</title>
    <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/titan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Titan on Astronomy posts by a computer geek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:37:46 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/tags/titan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Potential planets supporting life in solar system</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/potential_planets_supporting_life_in_solar_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/potential_planets_supporting_life_in_solar_system/</guid>
      <description>Potential planets supporting life in the solar system After a very long time, finally, I stopped procrastinating and start to write about astronomy again.
In this blog post, I go through the planets that potentially support life in our solar system. I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because scientists found new stuff recently and so many new news floating around.
Mars We are familiar with Mars, especially after successful Curiosity Rover landing. And it is getting more and more attractive as scientists make discoveries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Possibilities of life in the solar system, Saturn&#39;s moon Titan</title>
      <link>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_on_titan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 10:37:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://outofuniverse.madadipouya.com/post/life_on_titan/</guid>
      <description>Possibilities of life in the solar system, Saturn&amp;rsquo;s moon Titan Well, I have some exciting news about the possibilities of life in the solar system. But this time is not Mars or Europa, it&amp;rsquo;s about Titan, a Saturn&amp;rsquo;s moon. According to Reuters, data from NASA’s Cassini spacecraft reveals the existence of carbon in Titan. This speculates scientists about the possibilities of life under the icy ocean in Titan. My analysis, if the liquid water runs under the Titan icy ocean, the chance of microbiological life is higher than Mars.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>